<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>SOMsphere’s Blog</title><description>🚀 Suitable for Startups, Small Business, Sass Websites, Professional Portfolios, Marketing Websites, Landing Pages &amp; Blogs.</description><link>https://aayushgupta30.github.io/</link><item><title>MBA Interview Tips and Tricks</title><link>https://aayushgupta30.github.io/SJMSOM-Blog/mba-interview-tips-and-tricks</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://aayushgupta30.github.io/SJMSOM-Blog/mba-interview-tips-and-tricks</guid><description>As MBA interviews approach, Aakash Ezhilan and I reflected on our preparation and interview experiences, sharing insights to help fellow aspirants navigate the admission season with confidence. Best wishes to all MBA hopefuls for a successful journey ahead!</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Reflecting Over the Past Few Months</title><link>https://aayushgupta30.github.io/SJMSOM-Blog/reflecting-over-the-past-few-months</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://aayushgupta30.github.io/SJMSOM-Blog/reflecting-over-the-past-few-months</guid><description>Reflecting on my journey at IIT Bombay - SJMSOM, I&apos;m grateful for the transformative experiences and excited for the upcoming interviews. Best wishes to all prospective students - may your time here be as enriching and memorable as mine!</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Episode 2: Tanmay and Quizzing at IIT</title><link>https://aayushgupta30.github.io/SJMSOM-Blog/tanmays-quizzing-jounery</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://aayushgupta30.github.io/SJMSOM-Blog/tanmays-quizzing-jounery</guid><description>JDive deep into the world of quizzing with Mr. Tanmay on SOMCast! Learn how his love for reading fueled his passion for competition and the secrets to building a winning team.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Episode 1: Amartya and Filmmaking at IIT</title><link>https://aayushgupta30.github.io/SJMSOM-Blog/amartya-and-filmmaking-at-iit</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://aayushgupta30.github.io/SJMSOM-Blog/amartya-and-filmmaking-at-iit</guid><description>Join us on a captivating journey into the world of filmmaking with Amartya, a passionate SOM senior, as he unravels his extraordinary journey from mechanical engineering to the captivating realm of cinema!</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Navigating the MBA Interview: Insights from IIT Bombay - SJMSOM</title><link>https://aayushgupta30.github.io/SJMSOM-Blog/converting-sjmsom-call</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://aayushgupta30.github.io/SJMSOM-Blog/converting-sjmsom-call</guid><description>Discover firsthand insights into the interview process at SJMSOM, where a blend of personal introspection and domain knowledge is key to success. Learn how to articulate your journey and interests effectively in the panel&apos;s discerning eyes.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Exploring Life at IIT Bombay - SJMSOM: A Glimpse into MBA Excellence</title><link>https://aayushgupta30.github.io/SJMSOM-Blog/exploring-life-at-sjmsom</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://aayushgupta30.github.io/SJMSOM-Blog/exploring-life-at-sjmsom</guid><description>Dive into the MBA experience at IIT Bombay - SJMSOM, where academia meets synergy across disciplines, sports, and co-curricular vibrancy. Explore the essence of excellence in management education firsthand!</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Student Interview Experiences at SJMSOM, IIT-BOMBAY Part - 2</title><link>https://aayushgupta30.github.io/SJMSOM-Blog/interview-experience-sharing-2024-2</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://aayushgupta30.github.io/SJMSOM-Blog/interview-experience-sharing-2024-2</guid><description>Here is Part 2 of the interview experience of Arka Gohil, Bidisha Bose, Samarth Sharma and Amol Agarwal at SJMSOM, IIT Bombay. Gear up for more such videos from the batch of &apos;25.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Student Interview Experiences at SJMSOM, IIT-BOMBAY Part - 1</title><link>https://aayushgupta30.github.io/SJMSOM-Blog/interview-experience-sharing-2024-1</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://aayushgupta30.github.io/SJMSOM-Blog/interview-experience-sharing-2024-1</guid><description>Here is the Part 1 of the interview experience featuring Aditya Bose, Ankita Halder, Isha Sinha and Manav Jain at SJMSOM, IIT Bombay. Gear up for more such videos from the Batch of &apos;25.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>